

# MOCH ANJAR GANI A

As a UI/UX Designer and Frontend Developer, I am skilled in creating visually appealing designs and intuitive user interfaces, as well as coding the frontend implementation of these designs. With experience in creating content for social media, I understand the importance of user engagement and satisfaction.

#### **CONTACT:**

- Soreang, Kab Bandung
- @ anjargani89@gmail.com
- **\** 085963140823
- Web Portfolio
- **In** Anjar Gani

# SKILLS:

- Frontend Development (HTML,CSS, JavaScript)
- User Research, Analysis & Testing
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Design Software (Photoshop, Illustrator, XD & FIGMA)
- Project Management & Collaboration

#### LANGUAGE:

English

70%

### **CERTIFICATE:**

- Coursera (Foundations of User Experience Design)
- Rakamin Akademi (UI/UX Specialization)
- Dicoding (Swift & Kognitif)
- Digitalent (React Developer)

#### **EDUCATION:**

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering STMIK JABAR 2017-2021

GPA 3,05 of 4,00

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

## **UI/UX** Designer

Art Vatars INC - Jakarta Oktober 2022 - Present

- Designed website and mobile interfaces to meet the needs of the client and users.
- Conducted user research and testing to ensure that the design meets the desired user experience.

## **UI/UX** Designer

PT Inovatif 78 - Jakarta Juni 2022 - September 2022

- Created designs that meet the needs of the user.
- Worked with the development team to ensure the implementation of designs are accurate.

# UI/UX Designer & Frontend Develover

Universitas Muhammadiyah Bandung - Bandung Januari 2022 - Juni 2022

- Designed user-centered interfaces and implemented them using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Conducted user research to inform design decisions and improve user experience.

#### **Content Creator**

UC Signature - Bandung September 2021 - Desember 2021

 Created social media content to promote the company's brand and products.